Shiv Shankar Shambhu brothers, people often
ask me, don't you eat anything outside
?  But that is not the case at all, when
I travel on weekends or am on vacation,
I enjoy my favourite things.
I have just come to Nashik.   It is the
rainy season and the climate here is
very good.  So, early in the morning,
breakfast started with the famous Misal
Pav which had approximately 650
calories.  A chilled butter milk with it has
around 80 calories.  Then after that if you feel like
eating something sweet then Budha
Halwai's Jalebi is very famous here.  So, one
plate of this contains four pieces of jalebi
which has approximately 600 calories.  Then the
mini samosas here are also famous which taste like Kachori.
It contains approximately 300
calories.  Then after that we
reached Sayantara where Sabudana Vada
is very famous and this can be understood from the crowd of people.
So one plate [music]
comes with two sabudana vadas which had 500 calories.
Then there is the famous pineapple
juice which comes with ice cream, which is
very tasty and has about 350
calories.  Then to try something new, there
was Kadhi Bel here which is our
lumps, we mix this curry in it
and this entire plate had
approximately 450 calories.  Then finally,
after eating so much,
cumin soda for digestion.  So this means today I
consumed a total of 3150 calories.  But yes, today
I ate so much.  But I also know
how to balance it.  Tomorrow I will be
back to my routine and will cut out these
extra calories.  So
fitness doesn't mean giving up the things you love
forever, but
enjoying them wisely and with balance.